<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<article lang="en" slug="f1" featured="true" role="article" thumbnail="bundle://thumb.jpg">
    <metadata>
        <title>What is F1?</title>
        <description>Highest class of single-seater auto racing sanctioned by the Fédération
            Internationale de l'Automobile (FIA)</description>
        <author>Branden Sambersond</author>
        <canonical>https://www.formula1.com/</canonical>
        <note>This is an article that should be published on Monday</note>
    </metadata>
    <components>
        <image
            role="photo"
            bleed="true"
            unselectable="false"
            src="bundle://images/pits.jpg">
            <animation type="bounceIn" speed="slow" repeat="1" />
            <device mobile="true" tablet="true" desktop="true" />
            <caption> Racing Driver On A Pit Stop
            </caption>
            <credit>Quentin Tricoire</credit>
        </image>
        <text dropcap="true">
            <p>Formula One, also known as F1, is the highest class of single-seater auto racing
                sanctioned by the Fédération Internationale de l'Automobile (FIA). It is considered
                to be one of the most prestigious and competitive forms of motorsport in the world.</p>
        </text>
        <divider bleed="true" />
        <columns
            split="2-1"
            align="center"
            collapse="responsive">
            <column>
                <text type="text30">
                    <p>Formula One cars are the fastest road course racing cars in the world, with
                        the ability to reach speeds of over 200 miles per hour (320 km/h) on a
                        modern race track. The cars are designed and built by a handful of top-tier
                        teams, including Ferrari, Mercedes-AMG, Red
                        Bull Racing, and Williams, among others. Each team has a limited number of
                        engines and tires available for the season, which adds an element of
                        strategy to pit stops and race planning.</p>
                </text>
            </column>
            <column>
                <text type="text33">
                    <p>Races are typically held on purpose-built circuits or on public roads closed
                        for racing. The cars must be capable of reaching incredible speeds within a
                        very short distance, and the drivers must be skilled and experienced to
                        handle these high speeds and the intense
                        G-forces involved in cornering and braking.</p>
                </text>
            </column>
        </columns>
        <spacer size="very-small" />
        <container bleed="true" direction="vertical">
            <text type="text40">
                <p>
                    The Formula One season consists of a series of races held around the world,
                    known as
                    Grands Prix. The top drivers and teams are ranked based on their performance
                    throughout
                    the season, with the driver and team earning the most points being declared the
                    champion. The
                    season culminates in November with the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix, which also serves
                    as the
                    final race of the season.
                </p>
            </text>
            <video>
                <source>
                    <tiktok id="7397768134054169889" username="f1" />
                    <caption>Checo's just got that crazy eye aura </caption>
                </source>
            </video>
            <text type="text45">
                <p>
                    Formula One has a large global following and is widely considered to be one of
                    the most technologically advanced forms of motorsport. The sport is known for
                    its glamorous and wealthy owners, as well as its high-profile drivers, many of
                    whom have become celebrities
                    in their own right. The sport also has a long history of innovation, with new
                    technologies and materials constantly being introduced to improve performance.
                </p>
            </text>
        </container>
        <spacer size="very-small" />
        <text type="text39">
            <p>
                In addition to the on-track competition, Formula One is also known for its political
                intrigue and backroom deals, with teams and drivers often jockeying for position and
                influence within the sport. The sport has a complex and convoluted governing
                structure,
                with
                multiple layers of management and decision-making, which can sometimes lead to
                controversy and conflict.
            </p>
        </text>
        <spacer size="medium" />
        <gallery>
            <animation type="bounceIn" speed="slow" repeat="1" />
            <items>
                <item src="bundle://gallery/item-1.jpg" width="500">
                    <caption>Blue car</caption>
                </item>
                <item src="bundle://gallery/item-2.jpg" width="500">
                    <caption>Orange Car</caption>
                </item>
                <item src="bundle://gallery/item-3.jpg" width="500" />
            </items>
            <caption>Cars in F1</caption>
        </gallery>
        <text type="footer">
            <device mobile="false" tablet="false" desktop="true" />
            <animation type="zoomIn" speed="slow" repeat="none" />
            <p>Overall, Formula One is a highly competitive and technologically advanced form of
                motorsport that attracts a large global following and is widely considered to be one
                of the most prestigious forms of racing in the world.</p>
        </text>
    </components>
</article>