<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<article
    lang="en"
    slug="america"
    role="article"
    featured="true"
    sponsored="true"
    thumbnail="bundle://thumbnail/america-thumbnail.jpg">
    <metadata>
        <title>America</title>
    </metadata>
    <components>
        <image
            role="photo"
            bleed="true"
            unselectable="false"
            src="bundle://images/america/hero.jpg">
            <caption>Dumbo, Manhattan bridge, Nyc image</caption>
        </image>
        <text type="headline">
            <p>America</p>
        </text>

        <text>
            <p>The American Continent, also known as the Americas, refers to the landmasses that
                make up the Western Hemisphere, including North America, Central America, South
                America, and the Caribbean. This vast region stretches from the Arctic Circle in the
                north to the tip of
                South America in the south, and from the Atlantic Ocean in the east to the Pacific
                Ocean in the west.</p>
        </text>
        <spacer size="small" />
        <columns
            split="1-1"
            align="center"
            collapse="responsive">
            <column>
                <text>
                    <p>The American Continent is home to a diverse range of cultures, languages, and
                        landscapes. The northern parts of the continent, including Canada and
                        Alaska, are
                        known for their rugged mountains, vast forests, and icy tundras. In
                        contrast, the
                        southern parts of the
                        continent, such as Mexico, Central America, and South America, are
                        characterized by
                        dense rainforests, towering volcanoes, and arid deserts.</p>
                </text>
            </column>
            <column>
                <text>
                    <p>The history of the American Continent is rich and complex, with evidence of
                        human
                        habitation dating back over 15,000 years. The indigenous peoples of the
                        continent
                        have a long and storied history, with many cultures and civilizations rising
                        and
                        falling over the
                        centuries. European explorers and settlers arrived in the 15th century,
                        bringing
                        with them new technologies, ideas, and diseases that had a profound impact
                        on the
                        native populations.</p>
                </text>
            </column>
        </columns>
        <text type="blockquote">
            <p>Today, the American Continent is home to some of the world's most vibrant and diverse
                cities, including New York City, Los Angeles, Rio de Janeiro, and Mexico City. The
                region is also known for its rich cultural heritage, including music, art,
                literature, and
                cuisine.</p>
        </text>
        <text>
            <p>The American Continent faces a number of challenges, including climate change,
                economic inequality, and political instability. However, it is also home to some of
                the world's most innovative and forward-thinking countries, with many of them
                leading the way in fields
                such as technology, renewable energy, and sustainable development.</p>
        </text>
        <divider bleed="true" />
        <text>
            <p>In conclusion, the American Continent is a vast and diverse region that offers a
                wealth of opportunities and challenges. From the towering mountains of Alaska to the
                tropical rainforests of Brazil, this incredible landmass is home to some of the
                world's most unique
                and fascinating cultures, landscapes, and people.</p>
        </text>
    </components>
</article>