<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<article
    lang="en"
    slug="europe"
    role="article">
    <metadata>
        <title>Europe</title>
        <description>The Heart of the World: A Glimpse into Europe</description>
    </metadata>
    <components>
        <text type="headline">
            <p>Europe</p>
        </text>
        <divider bleed="true" />
        <text>
            <p>Tucked away in the northwest corner of the globe, Europe is a continent like no
                other. Comprising 50 countries, spanning over 10 million square kilometers, and
                boasting a rich history dating back to the ancient Greeks, Romans, and Vikings,
                Europe has been the
                epicenter of human civilization for millennia.</p>
        </text>
        <gallery role="mosaic" bleed="true">
            <items>
                <item src="bundle://images/europe/gallery/turkiye.jpg" />
                <item src="bundle://images/europe/gallery/spain.jpg" />
                <item src="bundle://images/europe/gallery/portugal.jpg" />
            </items>
            <caption>Countries</caption>
        </gallery>
        <container>
            <text type="title">
                <p>Geography</p>
            </text>
            <text type="text5">
                <p>From the snow-capped Alps in Switzerland to the sun-kissed Mediterranean beaches
                    of
                    Greece and Italy, Europe's diverse landscape is as varied as it is breathtaking.
                    The
                    continent's terrain ranges from rolling hills and verdant forests to windswept
                    moors
                    and towering
                    mountain ranges. The mighty Danube River flows through 10 countries, while the
                    majestic Rhine River carves its way through Germany and Switzerland.</p>
            </text>
            <text type="title">
                <p>Culture</p>
            </text>
            <text type="text5">
                <p>Europe is a melting pot of cultures, languages, and traditions. Each country has
                    its
                    unique flavor, shaped by its history, cuisine, and people. The continent is home
                    to
                    some of the world's most famous art, music, literature, and cinema. From the
                    works
                    of Leonardo da
                    Vinci and Michelangelo in Italy to the masterpieces of Vincent van Gogh in the
                    Netherlands, Europe's artistic heritage is unparalleled.</p>
            </text>
            <text type="title">
                <p>Cities</p>
            </text>
            <text type="text5">
                <p>Europe's cities are bustling metropolises that pulsate with energy and
                    creativity.
                    London's iconic landmarks, Paris' romantic atmosphere, Rome's ancient history,
                    and
                    Amsterdam's vibrant culture make each city a must-visit destination. The
                    continent's
                    cities are hubs
                    of innovation, entrepreneurship, and artistic expression, attracting visitors
                    from
                    all over the world.
                </p>
            </text>
            <text type="title">
                <p>Cuisine</p>
            </text>
            <text type="text5">
                <p>European cuisine is renowned for its rich flavors, aromas, and textures. From the
                    hearty stews and roasted meats of Eastern Europe to the pasta dishes and pizzas
                    of
                    Italy, every country has its unique culinary traditions. Don't forget the
                    delicious
                    pastries, cakes,
                    and chocolates that are an integral part of European baking culture.</p>
            </text>
        </container>
        <spacer />
        <text type="title">
            <p>Conclusion</p>
        </text>
        <text type="text6">
            <p>Europe is a continent that embodies the very essence of human civilization:
                creativity, innovation, diversity, and beauty. Whether you're interested in history,
                art, music, literature, or cuisine, Europe has something to offer everyone. So come
                and experience it for
                yourself – the heart of the world awaits!</p>
        </text>
    </components>
</article>