<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<article
    lang="en"
    slug="asia"
    role="article"
    sponsored="true">
    <metadata>
        <title>Asia</title>
        <description>The Land of Contrasts: Unveiling the Wonders of Asia</description>
    </metadata>
    <components>
        <image
            role="image"
            bleed="true"
            src="bundle://images/asia/hero.jpg" />
        <text>
            <p>Stretching from the snow-capped Himalayas in the west to the sun-kissed beaches of
                Southeast Asia, and from the vibrant streets of Tokyo to the ancient ruins of Angkor
                Wat, Asia is a continent that embodies the ultimate fusion of tradition and
                modernity. Home to
                over 4.5 billion people – more than half of the world's population – Asia is a land
                of contrasts, where ancient temples stand alongside skyscrapers, and bustling cities
                meet serene natural landscapes.</p>
        </text>
        <text type="title">
            <p>Geography</p>
        </text>
        <text>
            <p>From the towering mountain ranges of the Himalayas to the vast deserts of Mongolia,
                Asia's diverse geography is as breathtaking as it is varied. The continent is home
                to some of the world's longest rivers, including the Yangtze, Yellow, and Mekong,
                which flow
                through China, Japan, and Southeast Asia, respectively. The tropical rainforests of
                Indonesia and Malaysia provide a habitat for incredible biodiversity, while the
                Arctic tundra in Russia offers a harsh yet majestic landscape.</p>
        </text>
        <text type="title">
            <p>Culture</p>
        </text>
        <text>
            <p>Asian culture is a rich tapestry woven from diverse traditions, languages, and
                customs. Each country has its unique flavor, shaped by its history, cuisine, and
                people. From the ancient civilizations of China and Japan to the vibrant street life
                of India and
                Thailand, Asia's cultural heritage is a never-ending source of inspiration. The
                continent is home to some of the world's most revered philosophies, including
                Buddhism, Taoism, and Confucianism.</p>
        </text>
        <text type="title">
            <p>Cities</p>
        </text>
        <text>
            <p>Asia's cities are bustling metropolises that pulsate with energy and creativity.
                Tokyo's neon streets, Seoul's K-pop culture, and Hong Kong's financial hub make each
                city a must-visit destination. The continent's cities are hubs of innovation,
                entrepreneurship, and
                artistic expression, attracting visitors from all over the world.</p>
        </text>
        <text type="title">
            <p>Cuisine</p>
        </text>
        <text>
            <p>Asian cuisine is renowned for its rich flavors, aromas, and textures. From the spicy
                curries of India to the delicate sushi rolls of Japan, every country has its unique
                culinary traditions. Don't forget the delicious noodles, dumplings, and street food
                that are an
                integral part of Asian cuisine.
            </p>
        </text>
        <gallery>
            <animation type="flash" speed="slow" />
            <items>
                <item src="bundle://images/asia/gallery/sushi.jpg" />
                <item src="bundle://images/asia/gallery/moshi.jpg" />
                <item src="bundle://images/asie/gallery/rice.jpg" />
            </items>
        </gallery>
        <divider bleed="true" />
        <text type="blockquote">
            <p>Asia is a continent that embodies the very essence of human civilization: diversity,
                creativity, innovation, and beauty. Whether you're interested in history, art,
                music, literature, or cuisine, Asia has something to offer everyone. So come and
                experience it for
                yourself – the land of contrasts awaits!</p>
        </text>
    </components>
</article>